hello
beautiful
morning
me
P-A-T-R-I-C-I-A
welcome
qualification
learn
within
home
idea
ministry
education
continue
to find out
world
to sense
good
safe
here
place
safe
primary
fifth
sixth
you guys
to come
dad
mother
to come
grandfather
brothers
who
any
learn
together
Yes
to sense
good
week
before
explain
emotion
excuse me
show
plus
puberty
weather
change
body
P-U-B-E-R-T-A-D
to sense
emotion
within
when
ten
until
candy
age
about
remind
your
now
us
to accept
body
to select
search for
that
emotion
put
Name
now
to ask
Yes
can
handle
Yes
to sense
emotion
NN N
Yes
can
excuse me
handle
NN N
when
to sense
excuse me
weather
hard
emotion
around
good
your
to think
play
anger
brother
there
anger
first
friend
NN N
anger
no
comply
rule
no
agreement
me
before
play
brother
there
to win
me
mourn
shout out
me
anger
why
miss
me
let
play
be quiet
NN N
day
me
growing up
understand
tell
mother
me
understand
miss
emotion
control
reason
need
that
Meter
brother
there
me
patience
mother
Yes
NN N
patience
Yes
move along
relationship
link
me
impatient
less
better
Union
brother
now
friend
your
NN N
good
learn
control
anger
NN N
week
us
same.
to have
to accept
me
to sense
emotion
to think
that
do
control
me
Yes
learn
NN N
normal
positive
Yes
too
ir
environment
family
your
remind
objective
NN N
draw
history
own
to use
that
following
learn
today
start
objective
today
to select
excuse me
NN N
sort out
trouble
Yes
environment
good
there
who
Thank you
P-A-T-I
me
A-N-D-R-E-A
Contenta.
you guys
Yes
good
now
coexistence
remind
before
emotion
Yes
teacher
joy
grandfather
home
to want
grandfather
intelligent
one
day
grandfather
dad
mother
tell
grandfather
bedroom
to sleep
M-A-R-C-O
bedroom
A-L-E-X
different
emotion
each
watch
M-A-R-C-O
happy
watch
A-L-E-X
anger
Yes
good
identify
From
emotion
learn
before
joy
go to
emotion
remember
your
joy
go to
sadness
afraid
disgust
surprise
good
your
attentively
before
Yes
professor
example
to sleep
From
emotion
different
because
watch
before
emotion
different
equal
emotion
happy
excuse me
control
emotion
brain
connect
heart
do
excuse me